My dear children,
it is now better than several years
since l moved to New York
and l haven't seen you
as much as l would like to.
l hope you will come to this ceremony
of Papal honours,
More than all the money and power
on Earth.
You are my treasure.
Anthony and Mary,
although l entrusted your education to
your mother for your own best interest,
l look forward to seeing you, and to
a new period of harmony in our lives.
Perhaps you might prevail upon your
mother to come to this celebration,
and that from time to time, we can all
see each other at family functions.
Anyway, l remain your loving father.
Hail Mary, full of grace...
...blessed art Thou amongst women...
...and blessed is the fruit of Thy womb,
Jesus.
Holy Mary, mother of God,
pray for us sinners...
Almighty God, bless the insignia
of Saint Sebastian the Martyr,
that it may contribute to the sacredness
of him to whom it is given.
Do you, Michael, promise to be faithful
to the noble purposes of this Order,
to have a special care for the poor,
the needy and those who are ill?
l do so promise.
May the blessing of Almighty God,
Father, Son and Holy Spirit
descend upon you
and remain with you forever.
Vincent, our name is not on the list.
Write it in. Mancini. M-A-N-C-l-N-l.
- Problem?
- My name isn't on the list.
- Then you have to leave immediately.
- You want to dance with me?
Joe, it's Vinnie. These are our guests.
l'm sorry. l'm sorry, sir.
Welcome to the party.
- lt's good to see you.
- Good to see you. This is my husband.
- Sit down.
- My son, Anthony.
The Order of Saint Sebastian is one of
the highest honours the Church awards.
lt was first granted by Pope...
What about Mr Corleone's connections
with gambling?
The press kits have...
- And involvement with the underworld?
- Cut the crap.